[
  {
    "question": "Relationship status?",
    "answer": "I'll leave the relations to the database."
  },
  {
    "question": "How do you get the code for the bank vault?",
    "answer": "You checkout their branch."
  },
  {
    "question": "How did the developer announce their engagement?",
    "answer": "They `return`ed `true`!"
  },
  {
    "question": "Why did the security conscious engineer refuse to pay their dinner bill?",
    "answer": "Because they could not verify the checksum."
  },
  { "question": "What do you call a busy waiter?", "answer": "A server." },
  { "question": "What do you call an idle server?", "answer": "A waiter." },
  {
    "question": "How many Prolog programmers does it take to change a lightbulb?",
    "answer": "Yes."
  },
  {
    "question": "What diet did the ghost developer go on?",
    "answer": "Boolean"
  },
  {
    "question": "Why was the developer unhappy at their job?",
    "answer": "They wanted arrays."
  },
  {
    "question": "Why was the function sad after a successful first call?",
    "answer": "It didnâ€™t get a callback."
  },
  {
    "question": "Why did the angry function exceed the callstack size?",
    "answer": "It got into an Argument with itself"
  },
  {
    "question": "Whats the object-oriented way to become wealthy?",
    "answer": "Inheritance"
  },
  {
    "question": "Why did the developer ground their kid?",
    "answer": "They weren't telling the truthy"
  },
  {
    "question": "What did the array say after it was extended?",
    "answer": "Stop objectifying me."
  },
  {
    "question": "Where did the parallel function wash its hands?",
    "answer": "Async"
  },
  {
    "question": "What's the second movie about a database engineer called?",
    "answer": "The SQL."
  },
  {
    "question": "Why doesn't Hollywood make more Big Data movies?",
    "answer": "NoSQL."
  },
  {
    "question": "What did the spider do on the computer?",
    "answer": "Made a website!"
  },
  {
    "question": "What did the computer do at lunchtime?",
    "answer": "Had a byte!"
  },
  {
    "question": "What does a baby computer call his father?",
    "answer": "Data!"
  },
  {
    "question": "Why was the computer freezing?",
    "answer": "It left its Windows open!"
  },
  {
    "question": "Why did the computer squeak?",
    "answer": "Because someone stepped on its mouse!"
  },
  {
    "question": "What do you get when you cross a computer and a life guard?",
    "answer": "A screensaver!"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where do all the cool mice live?",
    "answer": "In their mousepads!"
  },
  {
    "question": "What do you get when you cross a computer with an elephant?",
    "answer": "Lots of memory!"
  },
  {
    "question": "How do programming pirates pass method parameters?",
    "answer": "Varrrrarrrgs."
  },
  {
    "question": "How do programming shepherds count their flock?",
    "answer": "With lambda functions"
  },
  {
    "question": "What airline do developers prefer when they're in a rush?",
    "answer": "Delta."
  },
  {
    "question": "How did pirates collaborate before computers?",
    "answer": "Pier to pier networking."
  },
  {
    "question": "Why don't bachelors like Git?",
    "answer": "Because they are afraid to commit."
  },
  {
    "question": "Why did the developer go broke?",
    "answer": "Because they used up all their cache"
  },
  {
    "question": "Are computers dangerous?",
    "answer": "Nah, they don't byte. They just nibble a bit."
  },
  {
    "question": "How did the mafioso kill the Node server?",
    "answer": "Tie await to it and let it async."
  },
  {
    "question": "What do you do when you can't understand your husband's behavior?",
    "answer": "man man"
  },
  {
    "question": "What do you call a doctor who fixes websites?",
    "answer": "A URLogist"
  }
]
